[{"question": "What is the brown object next to the plant? ", "answer": "A basketball", "category": "object recognition", "question_id": "1-1", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What is the object next to the keyboard?", "answer": "A globe", "category": "object recognition", "question_id": "1-2", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What is the object that books and a clock are on?", "answer": "A sofa", "category": "object recognition", "question_id": "1-3", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What is the object next to the boxes?", "answer": "A medicine bottle", "category": "object recognition", "question_id": "1-4", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What is the object that is leaning next to the yellow cabinet?", "answer": "An umbrella", "category": "object recognition", "question_id": "1-5", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What colors are sofa?", "answer": "Blue", "category": "attribute recognition", "question_id": "1-6", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What color is the mug?", "answer": "White", "category": "attribute recognition", "question_id": "1-7", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What color is the pair of shoes?", "answer": "White", "category": "attribute recognition", "question_id": "1-8", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What is the object drawn on the yellow bin? ", "answer": "A can", "category": "attribute recognition", "question_id": "1-9", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What is the color of the box underneath the white and purple box?", "answer": "Red", "category": "attribute recognition", "question_id": "1-10", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What is in between a pair of shoes and trash cans? ", "answer": "A ball", "category": "spatial understanding", "question_id": "1-11", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "Is there space to put a baseball underneath the table? ", "answer": "Yes", "category": "spatial understanding", "question_id": "1-12", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "Is there room for a chair in between the blue door and the blue sofa? ", "answer": "Yes", "category": "spatial understanding", "question_id": "1-13", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What is the furthest item on the sofa from the clock on the sofa?", "answer": "Keyboard", "category": "spatial understanding", "question_id": "1-14", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "Is elevator door opened or closed?", "answer": "Closed", "category": "object state recognition", "question_id": "1-15", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "Is the area light turned on?", "answer": "Yes", "category": "object state recognition", "question_id": "1-16", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "Is there natural light in the room?", "answer": "No", "category": "object state recognition", "question_id": "1-17", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "Are the books opened?", "answer": "No", "category": "object state recognition", "question_id": "1-18", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "I am tired and want to take a rest while waiting for the elevator to come. What should I do?", "answer": "Sit on the sofa", "category": "functional reasoning", "question_id": "1-19", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "Where can I store a trophy that I earned?", "answer": "A yellow cabinet", "category": "functional reasoning", "question_id": "1-20", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "how do I go down from the above floor to the below floor?", "answer": "use the elevator", "category": "world knowledge", "question_id": "1-21", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "What are the round shapes on the trash bins?", "answer": "Smiley faces", "category": "world knowledge", "question_id": "1-22", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "How can I enter a room?", "answer": "push or pull the blue door", "category": "world knowledge", "question_id": "1-23", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "How many elevators are there?", "answer": "2", "category": "object localization", "question_id": "1-24", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "Where is the white table?", "answer": "in between navy sofas", "category": "object localization", "question_id": "1-25", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "Where is blue door?", "answer": "Next to the sofa", "category": "object localization", "question_id": "1-26", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-1"}, {"question": "How many pairs of shoes are there?", "answer": "2", "category": "object recognition", "question_id": "2-1", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "If I want to study about Python programming language, what should I do? ", "answer": "Read the red book for Python programming language", "category": "functional reasoning", "question_id": "2-2", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "If I want to study about Python programming language, which color of the book I should read?", "answer": "Red", "category": "attribute recognition", "question_id": "2-3", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "I feel I need some suppliment, what should I do?", "answer": "Take the supplements on the round table", "category": "functional reasoning", "question_id": "2-4", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Do you think the hallway should be cleaned?", "answer": "Yes", "category": "world knowledge", "question_id": "2-5", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Is there any missing item?", "answer": "Yes", "category": "object state recognition", "question_id": "2-6", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Is there anything that may be spilling? ", "answer": "Yes", "category": "world knowledge", "question_id": "2-7", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Which ball has been moved?", "answer": "White ball", "category": "object state recognition", "question_id": "2-8", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Where is the yellow colored globe in terms of location of baseketball?", "answer": "Behind the basketball", "category": "spatial understanding", "question_id": "2-9", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Where can I sit and rest?", "answer": "Sit on the navy color sofa", "category": "functional reasoning", "question_id": "2-10", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "I need to work remotely at home. What items should I take?", "answer": "A mouse and keyboard", "category": "world knowledge", "question_id": "2-11", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Where is my missing shoe?", "answer": "Next to the plant", "category": "object state recognition", "question_id": "2-12", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Is there a hallway?", "answer": "Yes", "category": "spatial understanding", "question_id": "2-13", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Where can I possibly store my documents?", "answer": "Cabinet", "category": "functional reasoning", "question_id": "2-14", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "If I want to drink coffee, what should I use?", "answer": "A mug", "category": "functional reasoning", "question_id": "2-15", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "How many smiley faces are there on the trash cans?", "answer": "3", "category": "attribute recognition", "question_id": "2-16", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "If I want to do exercise, what should I use?", "answer": "balls", "category": "world knowledge", "question_id": "2-17", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "What sports can I play with items here?", "answer": "soccer or basketball", "category": "functional reasoning", "question_id": "2-18", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Is there red colored poster sticked next to the elevator?", "answer": "No", "category": "attribute recognition", "question_id": "2-19", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Where can I possibly check announcement?", "answer": "On the poster next to the elevator", "category": "functional reasoning", "question_id": "2-20", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Is there recyling bin for glass?", "answer": "No", "category": "attribute recognition", "question_id": "2-21", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Is there recyling bin for metal?", "answer": "Yes", "category": "attribute recognition", "question_id": "2-22", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "What is the latest location of white ball?", "answer": "In front of the elevator", "category": "spatial understanding", "question_id": "2-23", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}, {"question": "Is the plant bigger than the trash can?", "answer": "Yes", "category": "object state recognition", "question_id": "2-24", "episode_history": "caree-v0/caree-2"}]